

# **Agia Tyas Sakanthi**

- 089613122939
- ■ agiatyas10@gmail.com
- 9 Jl. Hamidrusdi III no 228G. Kota Malang
- Git https://github.com/agiatyas
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/agiatyas/

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Software Engineer (Frontend) having experience 3+ years of and contributed well to handling some projects using React JS, Umii JS, Next JS, and Vue JS frameworks. Experienced using Scrum, Trello, Jira, Notion and Git to support work management. I described myself as a creative, willing to learn, and care about healthy lifestyle. As a front-end developer I'm very interested in topics about web application development and UI/UX design. I also like to follow the IT community and like to collaborate, adapt, discuss with people who are experienced in the IT field.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Bina Nusantara (2020 - now) Majoring in Information System

SMK Telkom Malang (2016 - 2019) Majoring in Software Engineering

#### **SKILLS AND TOOLS**

- React JS, Umii JS
- Vue JS, Next JS
- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- · Material UI, ANTD, Chakra
- Redux State Management
- Axios
- GraphQL
- UI / UX Design
- Figma
- Redux State Management

## **COURSES**

MODERN REACT WITH REDUX UDEMY || 2024 MASTER CLASS REACT JS TAILWIND BWA || 2022 DIGITAL TALENT SCHOLARSHIP | KOMINFO || 2019

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### PT. Profeed Indonesia

July 2023 - now

 Develop Universe Application Backoffice for clients (Benteng Mas, Adinata, Seventeen Lounge, Maharaja) using Vue.js

# PT. Aplikasi Pekerja Indonesia (Jobseeker Company) | Frontend Developer

March 2022 - May 2023

- Develop Binar Academy's Careersite Website Application for Candidate Employee using React Js.
- Develop Internal Company's Careersite Website Application for Candidate Employee using React Js.
- Develop Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Careersite Website Application for Candidate Employee using PHP Codelgneter and Bootstrap.
- Develop Ranchmarket's Careersite Website Application for Candidate Employee using React Js.

# PT. Infosys Solusi Terpadu | Frontend Developer August 2019 - January 2022

- Develop CIMB Octo Clicks website (internet banking) phase I, II, and III using React Js.
- Develop CIMB Back Office Octo channel portal using Umii JS.
- Develop CIMB Back Office Config portal, Branch portal, and Landing page of 30 (Online Octo Onboarding) using Umii JS and Next JS.
- Develop BTN digital banking channel portal, and PPOB IBB BTN using React JS.
- Develop Corporate Internet Banking Victoria Bank using React JS.
- Develop BCA bank notes cabang website using React Js.

## PT. Ascope Teknologi Internasional | Internship July 2018 - September 2018

Develop web Publisher and Advertiser PT. Ascope using Angular.